logoease.com 2010-12-17

# Logo Ease Privacy Policy

Logo Ease is committed to protecting your online privacy while providing you with the most useful and enjoyable Web experience possible. While you can use many features of Logo Ease anonymously, you are required to provide personal information to gain access to some of our premium content and services.

**How we collect and use personal information**  
When you complete your logo and wish to save and download it we collect information about you and your business. The information we collect from you is never shared with any other company apart from [The Logo Company](http://thelogocompany.net/) and is treated as confidential.

**How we use "cookies"**  
As you probably know, "cookies" are small pieces of information that some Web sites store on your computer's hard drive when you visit them. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies but allow you to modify security settings so you can approve or reject cookies on a case-by-case basis. Even if you do not use cookies, you can still access all of the features on our site.

**What we provide to third parties**  
Logo Ease does not provide any third-party apart from [The Logo Company](http://thelogocompany.net/) access to your personal information.

**Obtaining your consent**  
By using our Web site, you give Logo Ease permission to collect information about the pages served to you as an anonymous user for the purpose of calculating aggregate site statistics.

If you are under the age of 18, you must not provide your name, e-mail address, or any other identifying information without the consent of your parent or guardian, or as otherwise provided for by applicable law.

Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**Safe place to shop!**  
McAfee SiteAdvisor confirms that [The Logo Company](http://thelogocompany.net/) website is a safe place to visit. You can read their report here: <http://siteadvisor.com/sites/thelogocompany.net>

**Tell us what you think**  
Logo Ease welcomes your questions and comments about our privacy policy. Please email us your comments via the contact us form.
